<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World SplashActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">The UEFA Champions League</string>
    <string name="rules">
        The UEFA Champions League  known
         simply as the Champions League and 
         originally known as the European Champion 
         Clubs Cup or European Cup is an annual
          continental club football competition 
          organised by the Union of European Football
           Associations (UEFA) since 1955 for the top 
           football clubs in Europe.1 It is one of the
            most prestigious tournaments in the world and 
            the most prestigious club competition in European
             football. The final of the 2011 tournament was the
              most watched UEFA Champions League final to date as well
               as the most watched annual sporting event worldwide 
               that year drawing 178.7 million television viewers.
Prior to 1992 the tournament was officially called the European
 Champion Clubs Cup but was usually referred to simply as the
  European Cup. The competition was initially a straight
   knockout competition open only to the champion 
   club of each country.1 During the 1990s the 
   tournament began to be expanded incorporating a 
   round robin group phase and more teams.1 Europes strongest national
    leagues now provide up to four teams each for the competition.The
     UEFA Champions League should not be confused with the UEFA Europa 
     League formerly known as the UEFA Cup.
The tournament consists of several stages.
 In the present format it begins in mid-July with three
  knockout qualifying rounds and a play-off round.5 The 10 surviving teams
   join 22 seeded teams in the group stage in which there are eight groups of four teams each.5 The eight group winners and eight runners-up enter the final knockout phase which culminates with the final match in May.5 The winner of the UEFA Champions League qualifies for the UEFA Super Cup and the FIFA Club World Cup.67
Real Madrid is the most successful club in the competitions history 
having won the tournament nine times including the first five seasons it 
was contested.8 Spanish clubs have accumulated the highest number of 
victories with 13 wins.8 The title has been won by 22 different clubs 12
 of which have won the title more than once.8 Since the tournament changed 
 name and structure in 1992 no club has managed consecutive wins with Milan
  being the last club to successfully defend their title in 1990.9 The reigning
   champions of the competition are Chelsea after beating Bayern Munich 4 on 
   3 on penalties following a 1 on 
   1 draw after extra time. 
</string>
</resources>
