<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World SplashActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name"> Faity tail Quiz</string>
    <string name="rules">
        Lucy Heartfilia is a 17-year-old celestial wizard who runs away from home to join Fairy Tail, a rambunctious wizards\' guild whose members are famous for their overly destructive antics. Along the way, she meets Natsu Dragneel, a boy who is traveling the land of Fiore together with his partner Happy, a blue flying cat, in search of his foster parent, a dragon named Igneel who had disappeared seven years earlier. Lucy is soon abducted by a renegade wizard posing as the famous Salamander of Fairy Tail. Natsu rescues Lucy, revealing himself to be the real Salamander and a Dragon Slayer, a wizard with the abilities of a dragon. After defeating the imposter, Natsu invites Lucy to join Fairy Tail.

Lucy forms a team with Natsu and Happy, where they take on various missions. They are joined by ice wizard Gray Fullbuster and armored female wizard Erza Scarlet, who investigate the actions of an illegal "dark" guild Eisenwald. Natsu and Lucy ignore the guild\'s rules to take on a high ranking "S-class" quest on Galuna Island, only to be joined by Gray and Erza. A rival guild Phantom Lord attacks Fairy Tail, resulting in war between the two guilds and Lucy being kidnapped; Fairy Tail eventually defeats the guild. The guild also crosses paths with Jellal Fernandez, Erza\'s childhood friend who is manipulated by Ultear Milkovich to revive the ancient dark wizard Zeref using the Tower of Heaven. Natsu defeats Jellal and the Tower of Heaven is destroyed. Two Phantom Lord members, Gajeel Redfox, a Dragon Slayer raised by the dragon Metalicana, and Juvia Lockser, a water wizard, join Fairy Tail. Laxus Dreyar, the renegade grandson of the guild\'s master Makarov Dreyar, attempts to take over Fairy Tail by setting up a battle royal, but is ultimately defeated and expelled.

Forming an alliance with the wizard guilds Blue Pegasus, Lamia Scale and Cait Shelter, Fairy Tail fights the dark guild Oración Seis who have revived Jellal. Wendy Marvell, a Dragon Slayer raised by Grandine and the sole member of Cait Shelter, joins Fairy Tail along with her flying cat Carla. Lucy, Natsu and the others enter the alternate universe of Edolas when their guild vanishes due to Edolas\' powers. The group encounters Faust, the king of Edolas who intends to bestow a limitless supply of magic for his universe by harnessing the magic and the people of Magnolia. Happy and Carla also discover their heritage as Exceeds sent to Earth-land as infants on the orders of their queen Chagot. Allying with the Exceeds and Faust\'s son Mystogan, Fairy Tail defeats Faust and restores their guild at the cost of Edolas\' magical power being drained. The group returns to Earth-land together with the Exceeds, one of whom, Panther Lily, forms a partnership with Gajeel.

Several members of Fairy Tail, including Natsu, Lucy, and their allies, participate in an exam on their guild\'s sacred ground of Sirius Island in which wizards can advance to a higher rank and thus take part in more dangerous missions. During the exam, Fairy Tail is drawn into a battle against the dark guild Grimoire Heart; the dark guild is seeking Zeref, who has been living on the island. Aided by a reformed Laxus, Fairy Tail defeats Grimoire Heart, and Zeref kills the guild\'s leader Hades. However, the incident summons the black dragon Acnologia, which attacks the island. The spirit of Fairy Tail\'s founding master, Mavis Vermilion, protects everyone on the island from Acnologia\'s assault with a defensive spell, freezing them in time.

After returning to Magnolia seven years later, the returning members of Fairy Tail discover their guild to be the weakest in the kingdom. The group participates in a tournament called the Grand Magic Games to decide the kingdom\'s strongest guild. Also participating in the tournament are Sabertooth, the current strongest guild, and Raven Tail, a guild founded by Makarov\'s resentful son Ivan. Fairy Tail additionally aids Crime Sorcière, a guild formed by an escaped Jellal, Ultear, and former Grimoire Heart member Meldy, in investigating a magical anomaly around the tournament arena. After defeating Sabertooth and Raven Tail, Fairy Tail claims first place in the Grand Magic Games. However, Natsu, Lucy and the others are drawn into a conspiracy involving the Eclipse Plan, which involves the use of the 12 Zodiac Gatekeys so that a person can travel back in time and destroy Zeref before he becomes a threat. Fairy Tail eventually wins the tournament but the Eclipse Plan is revealed to contain the dragons.


</string>
</resources>
