<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Ephesus Travel App</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">This application was made to help travelers explore Ephesus Ancient City and Nearby Attractions. By downloading our app you will have an ultimate guide to Ephesus, Turkey. App is all offline and when you download it once, you will not need any internet connection which will help you while touring around the ruins. Please feel free to send us e-mails for suggestions and missed points. Ephesus Offline Travel Guide uses information provided by severals sites and people.
Our to contributors are:\n

www.theephesus.com\n
www.ephesustoursbylocals.com\n
www.wikipedia.com\n
www.bestephesustour.com\n

You can book tours to Ephesus with our contributor websites and travel agents. Also you can find the greatests deals around Ephesus with our application. When you want to use deals around Ephesus, just contact us via our e-mail ephesus@turkeytravelapps.com\n\n
Privacy Policy of Ephesus Offline Travel Guide\n
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Ephesus Offline Travel Guide collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.turkeytravelapps.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Ephesus Offline Travel Guide.\n
Personal identification information\n
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the siteplace an orderfill out a formrespond to a surveysubscribe to the newsletter and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number,\n
Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.\n
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.\n
Non-personal identification information\n
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.\n
Web browser cookies\n
Our Site may use \"cookies\" to enhance User experience. Users web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.\n
How we use collected information\n
Ephesus Offline Travel Guide collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:\n
To improve customer service\n
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.\n
To improve our Site\n
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To process transactions
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To send periodic emails\n
The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.\n
How we protect your information\n
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.\n
Third party websites\n
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website\s own terms and policies.\n
Advertising\n
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Changes to this privacy policy\n
Ephesus Offline Travel Guide has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, . We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.\n
Your acceptance of these terms\n
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.\n
Contacting us\n
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:\n\n
Ephesus Offline Travel Guide\n
www.turkeytravelapps.com\n
09400, Aydin, Kusadasi, Turkey\n
+905321685216\n
ephesus@turkeytravelapps.com</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Slider Menu Opened</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Slider Menu Closed</string>
    
    <!-- Nav Drawer Menu Items -->
    <string-array name="nav_drawer_items">
        <item >Welcome screen</item>
        <item >Find People</item>
        <item >Photos</item>
        <item >Communities</item>
        <item >Pages</item>
        <item >Whats Hot</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <!-- Nav Drawer List Item Icons -->
    <!-- Keep them in order as the titles are in -->
    <array name="nav_drawer_icons">
        <item>@drawable/ic_home</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_people</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_photos</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_communities</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_pages</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_whats_hot</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_home</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_people</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_photos</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_communities</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_pages</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_whats_hot</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_home</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_people</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_photos</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_communities</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_pages</item>
        <item>@drawable/ic_whats_hot</item>
    </array>
    
    <!-- Content Description -->
    <string name="desc_list_item_icon">Item Icon</string>

</resources>
